几周之前 一个隐形的穹顶从天而降
A few weeks ago, an invisible dome crashed down
罩住了彻斯特磨坊镇 把我们和外部世界隔绝开来
on Chester's Mill, cutting us off from the rest of the world.
穹顶是怎么来的 其中蕴含着什么奥秘
Why the dome is here or what mysteries lie ahead,
我们还不知道
we still don't know.
每一天都试探着我们的底线
Every day it tests our limits,
我们内心深处的善与恶 一览无余
bringing out the best and the worst in us.
有人说我们会永远被困在这里面
Some say we'll be stuck here forever,
但是 我们决不放弃 坚持寻找逃出穹顶之法
but we will never stop fighting to find a way out.
大吉姆把蛋扔下了悬崖
REBECCA: Big Jim threw the egg off the cliff,
我想这证明了蛋就是穹顶的能源
I'd say that proves it's the dome's power source.
穹顶在收缩
The dome's contracting.
你是说它缩小了
You mean, it's shrinking?
我计算了穹顶收缩的速度
REBECCA: I figured out that at its present rate,
再过不久 穹顶就会
it won't be long before the dome.
- 把我们完全压扁 - 这一切都是你的错
- Crushes us completely? - All of this is your fault.
- 梅勒尼在哪 - 我画了一副景象
- Where's Melanie? - I painted a vision...
可能指示了我们救她的方法
it may show us how to save her.
梅勒尼 梅勒尼
- - Melanie! Melanie!
抓住我的手 抓住我的手
- Grab my hand! Grab my hand!
- 在我的梦里 我看到梅勒尼消失了
- In my dream, I saw Melanie disappear,
- 可我不知道原来预示那个样子 - 我爱你
- but I didn't know it meant that. - I love you.
你知道为什么吗
You know why?
因为她就该跟我在一起 吉姆
'Cause she's supposed to be with me, Jim.
我们必须去找梅勒尼
We have to go after Melanie.
太危险了 大家哪也不许去
It's too dangerous. No one's going anywhere.
- 能看到什么吗 - 看不到
- Can you see anything? - No.
哦 我的天啊 又是一次地震
Oh, my God! There's another earthquake.
你觉得这个坑通向哪儿
Where do you think the crater leads?
也许这是另一个隧道 就像学校里那个
Maybe it's another tunnel, like at the school.
- 可能通往顶点镇 - 也可能通往别的地方
- It could lead to Zenith. - Yeah, or somewhere else.
只要是外面 什么地方都行
Anywhere but here would be great.
我们一定要搞清楚
We've got to check it out.
但我们一定要想好怎么做
But we've got to do it right...
决不能让任何人冒生命危险
not risking anyone else's life.
救命 救命
Help me! Help!
- 波林 波林 - 让她侧躺下来 轻一点
- Pauline, Pauline! - Lay her down on her side, gently.
亨特 需要你的衬衫
Hunter, I need your shirt.
- 怎么回事 - 是莱尔 莱尔捅了她
- What happened? - Lyle. Lyle stabbed her.
- 那他去哪儿了 - 他死了
- Where is he now? - He's dead.
给
Here.
我试过给她止血了
I tried to stop the bleeding.
- 我们的急救设备都放在学校
- All our medical supplies are at the school.
那我们现在就过去
- Well, let's get there now.
普瑞斯就在树林边上 我们走
The Prius is at the edge of the woods. Let's go!
茱莉亚
Julia.
我在
I'm right here.
我被捅了之后 我看到了一副景象
After I was stabbed, I had a vision.
穹顶选择了你
The dome chose you.
但 不止你一个
But... you're not alone...
还有一个人 但我看不到他的脸
there's someone else, but I can't see his face.
他自己不知道自己是选中的
He... he doesn't know he's the one.
快 拿担架来 把担架放到她的下面
Come on, get a stretcher! Let's get this underneath her.
一定要压住她的伤口
Got to keep pressure on this wound.
- 瑞贝卡 你也跟我们一起来 - 好的
- Rebecca, you're coming with us. - Okay, okay.
- 好了 准备
- BIG JIM: Yeah. Yeah. Ready?
你会没事的
You're gonna be okay.
- 来 - 一 二 三 起
- Come on. - One, two, three... up!
保持呼吸
Keep breathing.
怎么回事
What's happening?
穹顶越来越近了
The walls are getting closer.
穹顶是半球形的 它水平方向和垂直方向
The dome's a sphere, it's contracting horizontally
都在收缩 我觉得穹顶在回缩
- and vertically... - I think it's shutting down.
在里面的所有东西都会被压成泥
Everything inside's going haywire.
是的 我们要找个传送装置 下到坑里探个究竟
Yeah, we've got to get some gear, so we can explore this crater.
救命 救命
Help! We need help!
从蒂尔登农场传来的
It's near the Tilden farm.
我以为所有人都去镇中央了
I thought we got everybody in the middle of town.
一定是汤姆回来拿什么东西
Tom must have gone back for something.
嘿 看好亨特
Hey, keep an eye on Hunter.
别做任何蠢事
Don't do anything stupid.
- 等等 你去哪里 - 我们要去找台笔记本电脑
- Wait, where are you going? - JOE: We need to get a tablet.
- 用来干什么 - 坑出现之后
- What for? - When this thing opened,
可能在穹顶里制造了一个新的裂缝
it might have created a new crack in the dome,
意味着我们也许能收到外面的WiFi信号
which means we may be able to get a Wi-Fi signal.
我们也许就能和戴安娜的爪牙取得联系
Maybe we can get a message to the Hounds of Diana.
如果爪牙们说梅勒尼就在顶点镇
If the Hounds tell us that Melanie's in Zenith,
那说明那个坑正是通往外界
that means the crater's our way out.
救命
Help!
- - Help!
怎么了 - 地震了 这东西塌下来了
What happened? - The shaking! It fell!
- 压到了我的腿 - 救救我爸
- It's crushing my leg! - Help my dad!
- 把他带走 把我儿子带出去 - 求你们
- Get him, get my son out of here. - Please...
- 不 我也要帮忙 - 和茱莉亚走吧 儿子
- No, I need to help! - Go with Julia, son.
- 你也要跟我们一起走 - 汤姆 我会照顾他的
- You're coming with us! - Tom, I'll look after him.
把他带出去
Get him out of...
我们试试这个
Let's try this.
- 孩子 跟茱莉亚走 - 我不会丢下你的 爸爸
- Buddy, go with Julia. - I'm not leaving without you, Dad.
- 我们会救他的 好吗 - 我在试试
- We're gonna help him, all right? - I'll try again.
走 出去 走 出去
Go! Get out! Go! Get out!
- 不要 爸爸 不要 - 走 快走
- No, Dad, no! - Go, go!
- 不 爸爸 爸爸 不 不 - 我觉得乔伊是对的
- No, Dad! Dad, no! No! - I think Joe's right,
- 穹顶在闭合
- that the dome's shutting down. -
我想我们只剩几个小时了
I'm guessing we've got a few more hours.
- 不 爸爸 不 - 来吧 孩子
- No! Dad, no! - Come on, buddy.
- 爸爸 - 我懂 孩子
- Dad! - I know, buddy.
我们走 快 伙计
- Let's go, come on, guys. -
把所有纱布都找来
Get as much gauze as you can find.
放在这儿 放在这儿
- Put over here! Put over here!
她的腹部很僵硬 内出血了
Her abdomen's rigid... she's bleeding internally.
莱尔可能捅到了某个器官 可能是肾脏 也可能是肝脏
Lyle might have lacerated an organ. Kidney, maybe, or her liver.
山姆 我知道你能就她 做些什么 好吗
Sam, I know you can help. Do something, all right?
要做手术来给她止血
She's gonna need surgery to stop the bleeding.
- 好 那快做啊 无论 - 我不是外科医生
- Well, then, operate. Do whatever... - I'm not a surgeon!
我们没有麻药和设备
And we don't have anesthesia or equipment.
没有核磁共振 我连是伤到哪个器官都不知道
I can't even tell which organ is injured without an MRI.
- 听着 肯定有办法的 快想办法
- Listen, there is an answer... - Find it!
- 求你 你一定要救救她 - 我会想尽一切办法的
- Please, you have to help her. - I'm doing everything I can.
穹顶之下
第二季  第十集
视频字幕由 SSK字幕组 制作发布
字幕只供学习 请勿做任何商业行为
敬请关注新浪微博@SSK字幕组
翻译：香蕉奶昔 呆毛 冬可可 Rubens Jophy
没有信号 很遗憾
No signal. I'm sorry.
不过这是个好主意
It was a good idea, though.
那 说明这个坑没有在穹顶里弄出裂缝
So, the crater didn't create a crack in the dome,
也就没有新的隧道
and there's no new tunnel.
也许有 但信号被谁屏蔽了
Maybe it did, but somebody's blocking the signal.
校对：爱吃 Jophy
是啊 也许是个混蛋杀人犯
Yeah, or maybe it's just a giant, killer suckhole.
再有几个小时我们就要被压扁了
We're literally hours from being crushed to death.
也许我就该去找我妈
Maybe I should just go find my mom,
时轴：络睿 压制：hhjie 总监：Jophy
和她一起度过最后的这几个小时
and spend my last few hours with her,
而不是在这儿说服自己
instead of trying to convince myself
那些控制着穹顶的王八蛋
that whoever or whatever controls this dumb dome...
会顾忌我们的死活
even gives a crap about any of us.
诺瑞 我需要你镇定下来 好吗
Norrie, I need you here with me, okay?
-嘿 嘿 你要干什么 -执行B计划
- Hey. Hey, wh-what are you doing? - Plan B.
乔伊 你不能下去
Joe, you're not going down there.
这是属于我的镇 现在也是你们的
This is my town... yours, too, now.
如果我们不做些什么 我们都活不了
If we don't do anything, we all die.
如果我们探一探这个坑
If we explore the crater,
那样我们也许能救出所有人
then we might be able to find a way to save everyone.
他说得对
He's right.
我们比别人更了解穹顶
We know the dome better than anyone.
你没事了 波林
You're okay, Pauline.
发生了什么事
What happened?
莱尔要把你从我身边夺走
Lyle tried to take you away from me.
他捅了你
He stabbed you.
不过他已经死了
But he's dead now.
一切都会好的 我保证
Everything's gonna be okay, I promise.
我们能给她止痛吗
Can we give her something for the pain?
我们有吗啡
We've got morphine.
只能用十毫克 好吗
Just ten milligrams, okay?
吉姆
Jim.
嗯
Yeah.
我们谈谈
We should talk.
好的 我马上回来
Okay, I'll be right back.
她看起来不错 在好转
She looks good... on the mend.
内伤太重了 不做手术无法控制
The internal damage is too massive to control without surgery.
那再想想别的办法
So, do something else.
我能让她尽可能感到舒服
I can keep her as comfortable as possible,
但我实在无能为力给她止血
but there is nothing I can do to stop her from bleeding out.
你什么意思 她会死吗
What are you saying, that she's gonna die?
如果还有什么办法
If there was something else...
任何办法 我都会去试
anything, I would do it.
我无法接受
I don't accept that.
波林是回来救我们的
Pauline came back to save us,
而不是在儿子面前失血而死
not bleed out in front of her son.
穹顶不会让她就这么死的
The dome won't let her die.
这是对她的另一个考验
This is just another test.
我的家庭 我的妻子
My family, my wife...
都是被穹顶选中的
we were chosen.
我们一定要把妈妈送到坑那里
We've got to get Mom back to the crater.
梅勒尼不是凭空消失的
Melanie didn't just disappear into thin air.
坑一定是通往什么地方
It must lead somewhere.
我也希望如此 朱尼尔
I hope it does, Junior,
但波林的伤太重了
but Pauline's injuries are too severe.
如果再去动她 会使失血加速的
If we move her, it will accelerate the bleeding.
那么 告诉我们能做什么
Well, tell me what we can do.
- 她需要增加体液 - 哪里有盐水
- She needs fluids. - Where do I get saline?
- 诊所 - 我去找
- The clinic? - I'll find it.
这是另一个隧道
It is another tunnel.
但和学校下面的那个不一样
But it's different than the one underneath the school
那些是什么
What are those things?
我也不知道
I don't know,
不过很酷
but they're cool.
是啊 还有点吓人
Yeah, and kind of terrifying.
好吧 我们接着走
All right, let's do this.
希望我们能在这下面找到梅勒尼
I hope we can find Melanie down here.
小心
Careful.
来
Come on.
你还好吗 妈妈
You okay, Mom?
就有点痛
Just a little pain.
我们能再给她注射一点吗啡吗
Can we give her... some more morphine?
不行 再注射就要过量了
We don't want to give her an overdose.
哦 朱尼尔 没事
Oh, Junior, it's okay.
爸爸马上回来了
Dad's coming back.
好吗 我们会治好你的 就像梅勒尼那样
Okay? And we're gonna fix you up... just like Melanie.
你觉得她没事吗 她逃出去了吗
Do you think she's okay? That she made it out?
什么事都有可能
Anything's possible.
把我的画笔和画布拿过来
My brushes and canvas.
什么意思
What do you mean?
我也许能画出我们出去的路
Maybe I can paint the way out.
朱尼尔 这很重要
Junior, it's important.
快去拿过来
Now go get them.
詹姆斯
James.
我们一起经历了这么多
We've been through so much.
我一定会看着我的小甜心 成长成一个男子汉的
I got to see my sweet, sweet boy become a man.
我爱你 妈妈
I love you, Mom.
我爱你
I love you...
永远
forever.
Forever.
你和朱尼尔说的
What you said to Junior...
像是永别
it sounded like a good-bye.
我们都了解事实
We both know the truth.
-我活不下去了 -我们只需要让你稳定下来
- I'm not going to make it. - We just have to get you stable.
如果那个陨石坑是出口，我们会带你出去的
If the crater's a way out, we'll take you.
不
No.
穹顶已经处置完我了
The dome's done with me.
我知道我自己会死
I saw my own death.
波林
Pauline.
朱尼尔才是关键
All that matters is Junior.
他要活下来
That he survives.
吉姆不愿意放弃我
And Jim won't let me go.
我不想那样
I don't want that.
你在胡说什么
What are you saying?
让我安详的去吧
Let me go peacefully.
贝姬 帮我吧
Becky, help me.
求你了
Please.
我以为你出现就为了这些
I think you were supposed to be here for this.
我不知道
I don't know about that.
我要去拿点装备 回到陨石坑
I've still got to go grab that gear, get back to the crater,
看看下面是什么
figure out what's down there.
我们应该分头行动
We should split up.
我带艾丹回学校 你继续去坑那边
I'll take Aidan back to the high school, while you head back.
好的 在学校等我
Well, wait for me at the school.
找山姆要一个对讲机 我们保持联系
All right? Grab a walkie from Sam. I'll be in touch.
宝贝 我们从这边走
All right, honey, we're gonna head this way, okay?
岔口要怎么走
What do we do about this fork?
哪一边
Which way?
我不知道
I have no idea.
看 乔
Joe, look.
我知道我们走哪边了
I think we just made our decision.
你觉得这个坑会开多长时间
How long do you think the crater's gonna stay open?
不知道 应该不长吧
I-I don't know. Not long.
我们必须去告诉芭比这里有可能是一个出口
We've got to tell Barbie there might be a way out.
快点 诺瑞 快点 乔 我们快走
Come on Norrie Come on Joe Come on let's go
嘿
Hey!
你们特么觉得自己在干哈
What the hell do you think you're doing?
-我们下去了 -废话 我看到了
- We went down. - Yeah, I-I see that.
不要做蠢事 这五个字你们不懂么
What part of "Don't do anything stupid" Did you not understand?
不要生气 我们不能等了
Don't be pissed. We couldn't wait.
我们发现更多的隧道了
We found more tunnels.
那里还有一直帝王蝶
There was a Monarch down there, too.
给我们指了一条尽头有光的道路
It-it showed us a path... with a light at the end.
你看到它去哪了么
Did you see where it goes?
里面一切都在摇晃 我们必须出来了
We had to get out, things are shaky down there.
通道不会开太长时间的
The passage may not be open for long.
这肯定是通向某个地方的
But it goes somewhere.
就像我之前说的 任意地方都比这儿好
And, like I said before, anywhere's better than here.
你老头好像
It doesn't look like your
不会再送蛋来了
dad's showing up with the egg anytime soon.
穹顶收缩的间隔时间越来越短了
The time between its contractions is getting shorter.
而且连带的让天气越来越糟了
And the dome's making the weather worse.
好吧 我们去坑底下
All right, well, we're going down the crater.
这是唯一选择
It's our only shot.
茱莉亚
Julia!
我们还有一个出路
I think we got another chance.
有可能出去
This might be the way out of here.
好的
Thanks.
山姆
Sam.
丽贝卡
Rebecca.
那个坑有可能是出路
The crater could be the way out.
我们快去聚集镇里的所有人
We've got to gather the town.
好的  所有人不是在这边就是在蔷薇酒吧那里
Okay, well, most everyone's either here, at the Sweet Briar,
-还有教堂 -好的 那就赶紧把大家聚集起来
- or the church. - All right, well, round them up.
-让所有人去树林 -怎么去
- We've got to get everybody to the woods. - How?
额
Uh...
搭校车
school buses.
校车是用柴油的  这里有很多游艇
They run on diesel. There's a whole fleet.
把艇里的柴油加到校车里
Got to be fuel left in some of them.
我去看看 把伤患聚集起来
I'll check it out. Round up the wounded...
我们先让他们上车
we'll get them on first.
好的 不能坐车的 就走过去
All right, anyone who can't fit on the buses will just walk.
吉姆 你在干嘛
Jim, what are you doing here?
在找生理盐水 有人受伤了
I'm looking for saline, someone's hurt.
额 你听到计划了么
W-Well, didn't you hear the plan?
我们要离开了 所有人
We're leaving. Everyone.
-你知道哪有盐水么 -不知道 别管了
- Did you find any saline? - No, leave it.
我们叫齐所有人
We have to round everyone up.
茱莉亚说 时间不多了
Julia said there isn't much time.
听着 如果没有生理盐水 我妻子会死
Listen, if I don't find that saline, my wife dies!
我就知道在这里 就等着我找来拿
I knew it! Like it was waiting for me!
嘿
Hey.
你妈妈在这
Your mom's here.
茱莉亚要我们把她抬到车子上
Julia wants our help loading up the buses.
怎么了
What's wrong?
你真的觉得我们能出去么
Do you really think we're gonna get out?
我知道 那个坑不稳定 但 是的 我们会出去的
I mean, the tunnels are freaky, but, yeah, we'll make it.
不是那些隧道的问题
It's not the tunnels.
我是说 隧道后面的事情
It's what's after that.
没有我妈妈 我还能回到
Am I just supposed to go back to my life in California?
我原本在加州的生活中去吗
Without my mom?
我怎么能够把她丢在这里
How can I go and just leave her here?
嘿 她不在这
Hey, she's not here.
安琪也不在了
Neither is Angie.
她们可能被埋在切斯特磨坊镇
They might be buried in Chester's Mill,
但她们一直都会陪在我们身边
but they'll always be with us.
你知道我为什么参加训练营么
Do you know why I was going to boot camp?
为什么我要来这
Why I'm here in the first place?
我猜是你惹上麻烦了
I assumed you got into some kind of trouble.
我打了一个蠢丫头一拳
I punched some stupid
她的牙都被打出来了
girl in the mouth and knocked her tooth out.
而她只是嘲笑了我的头发
And all she did was make fun of my hair.
现在一想到我是那么的介意就觉得自己好蠢
It's just so... stupid to think how much I cared.
-如果我不理她就好了 -不 穹顶要你来到这里
- If I had just ignored her... - No, the dome wanted you here.
即使不这样 也有用其它的方式让你进来的
It would have found another way.
我不在乎穹顶要什么
I don't care what the dome wanted.
我只要我的妈妈
Because I just want my mom.
困在穹顶的这些日子里 有时候我会想
Sometimes I think, on Dome Day,
如果我和安琪能和我妈妈一起吃上一顿早午餐就好了
if Angie and I just went to brunch with my mom...
但那样的话 我就不能遇到你了
But then I never would have met you.
我妈妈死之前告诉我要勇敢
My mom told me before she died to be brave.
但我现在一点也不勇敢
And I just don't feel brave right now.
听着
Look,
我不知道跟着会发生什么事
I don't know what's gonna happen,
但是 不管发生什么事
but, whatever's out there,
我们都会一起面对
we're gonna face it together.
好
Okay.
不
No.
波林 有新消息了
Pauline, there's news.
你开启的那条通道
The passage you opened...
我们打算让大家从那里出去
we're evacuating everyone through it.
所以 只要 只要你能坚持住
So, if-if you can just hold on,
我们就可以搏一把 就能带你去看医生
we can try and get you to a doctor.
我不行了
I won't make it.
我只会拖累我爱的人
I'll only slow down the people I love.
再坚持一下就好
It's just a little longer.
你可以的
You can do it.
不 这是穹顶想要的结局
No, this is what the dome wants.
我只是自作自受而已
I paid for my sins.
至少这一次 我可以一宿无梦 可以睡个好觉了
For once, I'll be able to sleep without dreaming.
不 现在我们有希望了
No, there's hope now.
多亏了你我们才能出去的
We're only getting out because of you.
这很好
Good.
朱尼尔会平安无事的
Junior will be safe.
啊 太痛了
Aah. This is so much pain.
求你 求你发发好心
Please... be kind.
求求你
Please.
啊 好心的女孩
Ah, sweet girl.
好心的女孩
Sweet girl.
你能帮帮我 确保每个人都有位置吗
Can you help me and make sure everyone has a seat?
-好 可以的 -谢谢 艾丹
- Yeah, okay. - Thanks, Aidan.
下雨了
Rain.
难道现在还不够遭吗
If it wasn't enough of a mess already.
穹顶的收缩肯定会
The dome's contractions must be
让天气状况变遭 或是之类的什么
messing with the weather patterns... or something.
不
No!
跟我来
Come with me now.
我都跟你说了一百遍了 我要留下
I told you a hundred times, I need to stay here.
妈妈 我是那四个人之一
I'm one of the four hands, mom.
-我必须帮忙 -我不是在询问你的意见 艾莉诺
- I have to help. - I'm not asking you, Eleanor.
嘿 嘿 嘿 诺瑞 帮我个忙 可以吗
Hey, hey, hey. Norrie, do me a favor, okay?
上第一趟车 到了洞口后
Get on this first bus, I'm really gonna need your help
我非常需要你的帮助
once we get to that crater.
好吧
Okay.
谢谢
Thank you.
好 快点
Okay, come on.
茱莉亚
Julia!
你看到安德里亚了吗
Have you seen Andrea?
她去拿供给品了 她在洞口和我们汇合
She's getting supplies. She's gonna meet us at the crater.
好 别发呆了 咱们走 快走
All right, don't stop. Let's go! Keep moving. Load up!
继续
Keep moving.
-嘿 波林呢 -她还在里面
- Hey, where's Pauline? - She's still inside.
我们在等吉姆从诊所回来
We're waiting for Jim to get back from the clinic.
他最好快点带着药剂回来
Well, he'd better hurry with that saline.
你妹妹怎么样了
How is your sister?
让我过去 我拿到药剂
Let me through! I got the saline.
好的 走
Got it, come on.
-我们得快点 -走吧
- We've got to hurry. - Let's go.
尽量帮助波林 然后我们得走了
Do what you can for Pauline, and then let's go.
一会见
I'll see you soon.
宝贝 我拿到了
Baby, I got it for ya.
我找到你需要的东西了
I found the stuff you need.
我告诉过你 穹顶会保护我们的
I told you the dome was looking after us.
波林
- - Pauline,
我回来了 亲爱的
I'm back, honey.
吉姆
Jim,
我不觉得疼了
my pain is gone.
那就好
That's good.
那真的太好了
That's good, that's real good.
我告诉过你会没事的
I told you it's gonna be okay.
我知道你爱我
I know you love me.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你不用说对不起
You don't need to be sorry.
不用说对不起
: You don't need to be sorry.
波林
Pauline?
看着我
Look at me.
发生什么了
What's wrong?
她的脉搏在变弱
Her pulse is dropping.
照顾好朱尼尔
Take care of Junior.
波林
Pauline...
我爱你们
I love you all...
你才刚刚重回我身边
I just got you back.
是你做的
You did this.
她说这是穹顶想要的结局
She said it was what the dome wanted.
她求我这么做
She begged me.
你总是知道该怎么做 不是吗
You always have the solutions, don't you?
我是为她好 我很抱歉
It was a kind thing to do. I'm sorry.
你总是知道
Always got something in your...
知道该怎么应对各种紧急情况
in your back pocket for every emergency.
那是她最后的要求了
It was her last request.
然后你就可以杀了她吗
Oh, now you can kill?
不顾她还是我的妻子
When it's my wife?
吉姆
Jim,
如果波林认为
if Pauline thought...
这是穹顶所想要的话
that this is what the dome wanted...
穹顶想让我们一家人团聚
The dome wanted my family together.
但是被你毁了
And you got in the way.
走开 吉姆
Walk away, Jim.
去找朱尼尔
Go find Junior,
带着他离开
and get him out of here.
我会永远想念我的妻子
I'll miss my wife forever.
但没人会想念你
No one's gonna miss you.
妈妈
Mom?
Mom!
妈妈
天呐
Oh, my God.
山姆
Sam.
你还好吗
- - You ok?
起来
Get up.
发生了什么
What happened?
不 不
Oh, no. No!
我妈妈在哪
Where's Mom?
她死了
She's gone.
-什么意思 -波林让丽贝卡帮她
- What do you mean? - Pauline asked Rebecca to help her...
结束她的生命
end her life.
她太痛苦了
She was in so much pain.
吉姆要向丽贝卡复仇了
Jim went after Rebecca.
我试着阻止他 但是我失败了
I tried to stop him, I couldn't.
我很抱歉 朱尼尔
I'm so sorry, Junior.
妈妈那时是在跟我告别
Mom was starting to say good-bye.
我早该明白的
I should have known.
我们得去找你的父亲 他完全失去理智了
We've got to find your dad... he's gone crazy.
-我们得去劝服他 -我为什么要这么做
- We've got to talk him down. - Why would I do that?
劝服对他来讲从来都没有用 只能和他做交易
There's no talking to him, there's only dealing with him.
你为什么要画那幅画 波林
Why'd you paint that, Pauline?
我真希望你没画过
I wish you hadn't.
穹顶
Dome...
我们做个交易
I'll make you a deal.
如果你能立刻把她带回来
If you bring her back right now...
我就答应不会伤害任何一个
I won't murder every single one
你的那些特殊的小朋友们
of your special little friends.
我就不撕碎茱莉亚的喉咙
I won't slit Julia's throat,
不一枪毙了芭比
shoot Barbie in the heart,
不活活烧死那些孩子们
or burn those kids alive.
怎么样
Okay?
给你三秒考虑
You got three seconds.
那好吧
Okay then.
我会让你彻底的自由
I'm gonna free you from all this.
穿过穹顶 远离这里的一切
So you can go right through that dome wall.
穹顶会后悔它对我们所做的这一切
And it's gonna regret what it did to us.
我保证
I promise.
这次和我们以前的计划一样
This is the same plan that we had before.
我们分成几个小组
We're all gonna break up into small groups,
一家人在一个组里
keeping your family with you.
我们会一个一个的叫你们的名字 然后送你们下去
We will call you forward one-by-one and get you down.
等到一个组的人齐了
Once your entire group is down,
乔和诺丽就带你们去
Joe and Norrie, here, will guide you into...
你怎么知道这样做是安全的
How do you know this is safe?
我知道 因为我以前这么做过
I know because I've done it before.
听着 我知道你们都很害怕
And, look, I know you're all scared.
我也知道我只是个陌生人
Okay? I-I-I know that I'm a stranger.
但是在过去的两周里 我们都为了这个小镇
But for the last two weeks, we have fought together
的生存而一起战斗过
for the survival of this town.
现在 我需要你们相信我
But, right now, I need you to trust me.
因为我们没有其他的选择了
'Cause we don't have another choice.
如果继续待在这里 我们就只有死路一条
If we stay here, we die.
所以 走吧
Now, come on!
我们一起离开这儿
Let's get out of here!
卡洛琳 听着 我要你跟着我一起下去 好吗
Carolyn, listen... I need you to go down with me, okay?
帮我让他们保持镇定
Help me keep everyone calm.
茱莉亚 亨特
Julia, Hunter.
嘿 你们两个待在这上面好吗
Hey, can I get you guys to stay at the top here?
保持这里的秩序
All right? Keep everything orderly.
保证我们没有漏下任何人
Make sure we don't leave anyone behind.
我遗漏什么了吗
Am I forgetting anything?
没有
No.
你该做的都做了
You're doing exactly what you're supposed to.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
好了 大家准备好了吗
All right, you guys ready?
开始行动吧
Let's do it.
来吧 第一组 跟着我
All right, everybody... group one, stick with me.
镇定点 我们会没事的
Just stay calm, all right? We're gonna be fine.
走吧
Let's go.
等一下 等一下
Hold on, hold on.
没事的 大伙儿 我们以前来过这
It's okay, guys... we've been here before.
没必要害怕
There's no need to be afraid.
小心
Careful.
好的 卡洛琳
All right, Carolyn.
小心
Watch out!
裂缝正在扩大
Crack's getting wider.
-你没事吧 -没事
- You okay? - Yeah.
好的
All right.
所有人注意自己的脚下
Everybody watch your step, all right?
我们帮助你们过去
We'll help you cross.
现在情况怎么样了
Okay, how are we doing?
大部分人都明白该做什么了
Most folks are accounted for.
朱莉娅 你可千万在线啊
Julia, please be there.
安德丽亚
Andrea?
怎么了 你在哪
What's wrong? Where are you?
我在家里 我需要帮助 我 噢 我的天
I'm at my house. I need help, I... Oh, God!
安德丽亚 安德丽亚
Andrea? Andrea!
安德里亚
Andrea.
Andrea?
安德里亚
在这
In here.
我就知道你会跑过来
I knew you'd come running.
把球棒放下
Put the bat down.
茱莉亚 快回答
Julia, come in.
- 别多嘴 - 茱莉亚
- Less is more. - Julia?
山姆 怎么了
Hey, Sam. What do you need?
你那没事吧
You okay?
嗯 我在帮安德里亚
Yeah, I'm just helping Andrea.
我们现在就过去了
We're headed back now.
我和朱尼尔还有亨特都在洞口这里
Junior and I are at the crater with Hunter.
有件事要告诉你
Listen, you should know, um...
波林死了
Pauline is dead.
还有吉姆杀了贝丽卡
And Jim killed Rebecca.
他现在一定藏在某个地方
He's out there somewhere.
先不说了 山姆
Got to go now, Sam.
你想要怎样 吉姆
What are you doing, Jim?
报复
Payback.
为什么针对我
Against me?
我除了把你当邻居和朋友看待以外
What did I ever do,
做过什么对不起你的事吗
except be your neighbor and friend?
这与你无关 亲爱的
It's not about you, honey.
山姆还忘了告诉你 是贝丽卡谋杀了波林
Sam forgot to mention that Rebecca murdered Pauline.
我给过穹顶机会 让它把波林还给我
Yeah. I gave the dome a chance to return her to me,
但是它拒绝了
but it declined.
所以你就遭殃了
Which is bad for you.
杀了我 也不会让波林起死回生
Killing me... won't bring Pauline back.
是的 不过这样也许能毁掉穹顶的某些计划
Yeah, but it might ruin some of the dome's plans.
这就足够了
And that's good enough.
安德里亚可是你的朋友
Andrea was your friend.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
所以我把她结果的很迅速
That's why I killed her quick.
你就没有这么好运了
You don't get that privilege.
你知道为什么穹顶不把波林救回来吗
Do you know why the dome didn't bring Pauline back?
因为你就是个笑话
Because you're a joke.
穹顶不会让你这种人渣称心如意的
'Cause the dome doesn't make deals with insects like you.
甚至你老婆都觉得你无能
Even your wife knew you were meaningless.
等你嘴巴被砸烂了以后 或许会更讨喜欢一点
I'm gonna like you a lot better with your mouth broken.
好了 大家都跟上 继续向前走
All right, everybody. Come on. Keep moving forward.
继续往前 你们会和后面的人汇合的
Keep moving forward, you'll catch up with the next group.
继续走下去 好吗
All right? Let's go.
大家都会没事的
Everything's gonna be fine.
茱莉亚 还剩多少人
All right, Julia... how many we got left?
呃 只剩不多 我马上送他们下去
Uh, only a few... I'm sending them down now.
茱莉亚呢
Where's Julia?
她去帮她朋友了
She left to help a friend.
她现在到底在哪
Where is she right now?
我不知道 对讲机也没回应
I don't know... she's not answering her walkie.
茱莉亚
Julia!
我在这
Here!
你还好吗
Are you okay?
吉姆把安德里亚杀了 现在正在追杀我
Jim killed Andrea, he's behind me.
- 朱尼尔 - 别管我 你们走
- Junior. - Go without me.
- 不 我不会让你一个人去的 - 我说了 你们赶紧走
- No, no. I'm not gonna let you go alone. - I said... go!
搭我肩上
Put your arm around me.
你想干什么 儿子
What are you doing, son?
我不再是你儿子了
I'm not your son anymore.
我不会让你再伤害任何人
I'm not gonna let you hurt anyone else.
那你打算怎么做
How you gonna do that?
我不会让你离开这座小镇的
You're not leaving this town.
这可由不得你说了算
You don't tell me what to do.
由不得你
Not you.
也由不得穹顶
Not the dome.
这是我的小镇 小朋友
This is my town, little boy.
那你就最后享受一下这里吧
Enjoy what's left of it.
天呐 你总算来了
Oh, God. You made it.
发生什么了
What happened?
- 是吉姆 - 他在哪
- Jim. - Where is he?
现在没时间了 芭比
Barbie, there's no time.
把他留给朱尼尔处理了
Junior's taking care of it.
吉姆不会来到这下面了
Jim's not getting down here.
好吧 我来扶她
All right. I'll take her.
我们走
Let's go.
你能带着艾丹先走吗
Can you take Aidan up ahead?
只管往前走 好吗 我就在后面跟着你们
You just go on, all right? I'll be right behind you.
- 好 - 走吧
- Okay. - Come on.
亨特 追上乔和诺瑞 告诉他们赶紧走
Hunter, go up front with Joe and Norrie. Tell them to move out.
- 好吗 - 好的
- All right? - Okay.
我们也跟着
We'll catch up.
慢慢来
Nice and slow.
朱尼尔
Junior!
好了
All right.
你得跳过去
You're gonna have to jump.
觉得能做到吗
Think you can do it?
可以 我能跳过去
Yeah, I can make it.
我先过去再帮你
I'll get across and I'll give you a hand.
好了 过来吧
All right. Come on.
- 站过来 把手给我 - 好
- Step up, give me your hand. - Okay.
我过不去了
I can't make it.
不 一定还有别的方法 我不会把你留在这的
No, there's got to be another way. I'm not leaving you here.
你没有别的选择
You don't have a choice.
小镇需要你 你得快点
The town needs your help, and fast...
通道马上就要塌了
before the tunnels cave in on them.
可是穹顶选择了你
The dome chose you.
芭比 听我说
Barbie, listen to me.
波林看到了幻象
Pauline had a vision
有人会带领我们逃离穹顶
of someone guiding everyone out of the dome.
她没有看清他的脸 但那个人就是你
She didn't see his face, but it's you.
但是我们为这个镇所做的一切 都是携手一起做到的
But everything we've done for this town, we've done together.
没关系 穹顶已经指引我们走到现在这个地步
It's okay. The dome has gotten us this far.
我相信
I have faith...
只要你能按照它的意愿行事
that if you do what it's asking...
它就会保护我的
it will protect me.
我会回来找你
I'm coming back for you.
我知道
I know.
朱尼尔
Junior!
朱尼尔 你不能丢下我
Junior, you can't leave me!
朱尼尔
Junior!
芭比 茱莉亚在哪
Barbie, where's Julia?
她在后面 她让我先过来
She's coming. She sent me up ahead.
为什么大家都停下了
Why's everybody stopped?
没人知道该走哪条路
Nobody knows which way to go.
芭比 我们应该走这条
Barbie, we need to go this way.
我们看见有只蝴蝶飞去了这边
We saw the butterfly go down there.
我觉得这是个指示
I think it's a sign.
我和乔都这么觉得
Both Joe and I do.
好了 我们走这边
All right, this is the way.
听到了吗
Okay?
大家都跟着我
Everybody follow me.
发生什么了
What happened?
芭比先走了 他会回来找我们的
Barbie went ahead, he'll come back for us.
然后我们再想办法过去
Then we'll figure out a way across.
不 这里不该是条死胡同的
No, this can't be all that's there.
- 不可能 - 这里面就只是个洞穴吗
- It can't be. - Is this a cave in?
芭比 我们现在怎么办
Barbie, what do we do now?
我 我也不知道
I don't... I don't know.
我们一路走来结果只是个死胡同吗
We didn't come all this way for a dead end.
你妹啊
Screw you!
听到了吗
Can you hear me?!
不管是谁在操控这一切
Whoever you are controlling all of this,
就不能告诉我们到底是怎么一回事吗
can you just talk to us and tell us what's going on?!
你是怎么
How did you...?
我也什么都不知道
I have no idea.
这是什么声音
What's that noise?
梅勒尼
Melanie?
跟着我
Follow me.
我们回家吧
We're going home.